{
    "id": "baaf4af299094528b020627a6161599c",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is worse ………………… I thought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………. young to get married.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "China is …………….. India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bigger than",
                "bigger then",
                "as big"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………. in the team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "the best",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not as tall ………………….. she is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Even a sweeper earns …………………. I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more then",
                "more than",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was …………………. girl I have ever seen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prettiest",
                "the prettiest",
                "the most pretty"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The day was ………………….. hot that we didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They would like …………………. information about the subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "further",
                "farther",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The museum has got ………………….. collection of antique objects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fine",
                "finest",
                "the finest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}